亲爱的  你绝对会爱死我今年的万圣节服装
Honey, you are going to <i>love</i>my Halloween costume this year.
但你绝对会更喜欢我的服装
But not as much as you are gonna <i>love</i> mine.
不可能  你会更喜欢我的
No, you're gonna love <i>mine</i> more.
-不可能  你会更喜欢我的  -你俩
-No, you're gonna love mine more. -Guys!
把这种诡异的气氛留到晚上
Save the creepiness for tonight.
先声明下  我今年不带查莉玩不给糖就捣乱了
By the way, I can't take Charlie trick-or-treating this year.
我自己有安排了
I've got plans.
我和艾薇也不成
Ivy and I can take her.
我们会去参加一个派对  但是不会回来太晚的
We're going to a party, but that's not until later.
想知道我的安排是什么吗
You wanna know what my plans are?
好了  我憋不住了
Okay, you forced it out of me.
我要去约会
I am going out.
和个女生
With a girl.
难道艾米特又要扮成碧昂斯吗
So is Emmett going as Beyonce again?
她叫佐伊  是我给她送去的炸鸡
Her name is Zoey, and I met her while delivering chicken...
两份鸡腿肉  肉汁在旁边
Two piece, dark meat, gravy on the side.
-厉害  听起来不错  -是啊
-Wow, she sounds great. -I know.
她可有意思了  你们绝对会喜欢她的
She's a lot of fun. You're gonna love her.
已经喜欢上她了
Love her already.
别这样
Stop that.
听着  对于我来说  很高兴听到
Well, I for one am glad to hear.
PJ度过了斯凯勒时期  而开始结交新女孩
That P.J. Has gotten over Skyler and has found a new girl.
嘿  只要不用再看到
Hey, so long as I don't have to look.
碧昂斯·艾米特  我就知足了
At Beyonce Emmett, I'm happy.
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第二十五集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E25  Scary Had A Little Lamb
-万圣节快乐  达布尼太太  -你想干什么
-Happy Halloween, Mrs. Dabney. -What do you want?
我看你是为了万圣节提前穿上了女巫服装
I see you put on witch Halloween costume early this year.
依我看来  你又扮成了邪恶魔鬼的孩子
And I see you're going as evil monster devil child again.
噢  今年新加了”邪恶“这个词  真犀利
Oh, you added the word "evil" this year. Nice touch.
我喜欢新鲜感
I like to keep it fresh.
不闲扯了  我们来谈谈每年
Anyhoo, I'm here to talk about the trouble.
万圣节你所遭遇的不幸
That you always have on Halloween.
你所指的不幸  难道是指从十一年前
You mean the trouble that started 11 years ago.
你学会了如何走路那时的事吗
About the same time you learned to walk?
每年你的树上都挂满了卫生纸
Every year, your trees get toilet paper
房子都被鸡蛋袭击
and your house gets egged.
只需五十美元  我会保证这些一去不复返
For just $50, I can make sure that stops.
这么说来  你来保护我
So you're offering me protection...
来免受于你的折腾
From <i>you.</i>
是一个无名小流氓
From an unnamed hooligan.
叫盖比
Named Gabe.
是谁伤你这么深  让你对这个世界失去了信任
Who hurt you so bad that you can't trust?
好了  服了你了  反正我也别无选择
All right, fine. I guess I have no choice.
-就这么定了  -定了
-You've got a deal. -All right.
我拿到那五十美元后  咱俩就不再纠缠
I'll just take that 50 and we'll move on with our lives.
我手头可没有五十美元的闲钱
I don't have that kind of money just sitting around.
给我一点时间去凑
I'm gonna need a little time.
好吧
All right.
你最好快点儿
You better hurry.
因为这个时节天黑得特别早
It gets dark very early this time of year.
我爱万圣节
I love Halloween.
彼此彼此
So do I.
听着  查莉  正如你所见
Well, Charlie, as you can probably see.
咱们邓肯家对万圣节
Us Duncans take Halloween.
那是相当的重视
Very seriously.
我回来了
<i>I'm home.</i>
噢  我们来看看这是谁
Oh, I wonder who that could be.
天啊  是老爸
Wow, it's dad!
嗨  我是鲍伯
Hi, I'm Bob.
鲍伯到  害虫跑
Of Bob's bugs be gone.
你家有害虫吗
How's your vermin?
我回来了
I'm home!
快看啊  难道这是  阿什丽·提斯代尔
Well, if it isn't... Ashley Tisdale?
我是老妈啊
I'm mom,
我是大明星
And I'm a <i>star.</i>
闪瞎你的眼
Ba-bam!
搞什么  好吧  好吧  我不是个灭虫专家
Yeah? Well well, I'm not an exterminator.
我是个害虫控制专家
I'm a pest control specialist.
我曾和你说过
Did I ever tell you about the time
我以前上的是西南丹佛社区大学吗
I went to southwest Denver community college?
我要甜甜圈  我要甜甜圈
Me want donut. Me want donut.
好了  情况一发不可收拾
Well, things are getting a little ugly.
我们感恩节再见
We'll see you at Thanksgiving.
嘿  盖比  你的万圣节服装呢
Hey, Gabe. You gonna put on your costume?
嘿  大家好
Hey, everybody.
-你这是什么名堂  -我是个长着胡子的哥特人
-What are you supposed to be? -I'm a goth wearing a mustache.
你这套服装够怪的
That's kind of a weird costume.
没有小波比怪
Not as weird as little bo peep.
（《小波比》：美国童谣）
其实  说这是小波比有点不合适
Well, actually, the little bo peep costume wasn't appropriate...
因为这套服装少了丝性感  多了份可爱
There was not enough bo, a little too much peep.
-臭美  -其实我扮的是玛丽
-Hmm. -No, I'm Mary.
来自《玛丽有只小羊羔》
From "Mary Had a Little Lamb ."
（《玛丽有只小羊羔》：美国童谣）
噢  我差点儿忘了一件事
Oh! But I seem to be missing something.
就是小羊羔
Oh, little lamb.
-查莉  大声说出来  -咩
-Go ahead, Charlie, say it. -Baa.
怎么是胡萝卜  糖在哪呢
Carrots? Where's the candy?
噢  我们今年不发糖
Oh, we're not giving out candy this year.
我觉着发一些更健康的零食比较好
I thought it would be fun to hand out healthy snacks instead.
你想让这房子被扔鸡蛋吗
We're gonna be <i>that</i> house?
我们的第一批小鬼
<i>Our first trick-or-treater.</i>
胡萝卜  你想被扔鸡蛋啊
Carrots? You're <i>that </i>house?
艾薇  我们要去化妆派对  你的服装呢
Ivy, we're going to a costume party. Where is your costume?
看好了  俺已经穿上了
Oh, I've got a costume.
太逼真了
That is so real.
俺本想弄把菜刀在头上
I was gonna put the cleaver on my head,
但俺可不想让菜刀抢了俺这张脸的风头
But I didn't wanna compete with all this.
-不给糖就捣乱  -我的七舅姥爷  是只泰迪熊
-Trick or treat! -Oh my gosh, a Teddy bear.
太有爱了  知道吗  我的名字就是泰迪
That is so adorable. You know, my name is Teddy.
不给糖就捣乱
Trick or treat!
拿好了  泰迪熊
Here you go, Teddy bear.
胡萝卜  你开玩笑呢吧
Carrots. You're kidding, right?
泰迪熊有点儿小脾气
Teddy bear's got a little 'tude.
-万圣节快乐  -我谢你了
-Happy Halloween. -Thanks.
不用敲门了
Don't bother.
达布尼太太
Mrs. Dabney?
滚开  这是自动答复
Go away! This is a recording!
我是盖比啊
It's Gabe!
哼  够讽刺的
Huh! Ironic,
我一直在想办法让你的脑袋搬家
Considering all the times I've thought about removing your head.
我是来取那五十美元的
I'm here for my 50 bucks.
-先把这个签了  -什么东西
-First sign this. -What is it?
一份合同保证书
A contract guaranteeing.
来保证今晚我的房子不会受到任何威胁
That nothing's gonna happen to my house tonight.
在你把不捣乱就给糖的小鬼招来之前  赶紧消失
Now go away before you attract the treat-or-trickers.
你是想说不给糖就捣乱吗
You mean the trick-or-treaters?
无所谓了  反正我恨这个节日
Whatever. I hate this holiday.
我去开门
<i>I've got it.</i>
-嘿  -嗨
-Hey. -Hi.
佐伊  这是我老妈  其实是我老爸
Zoey, I'd like you to meet my mom... I mean my dad...
天啊  你俩的服装太给力了
Guys, your costumes are too good.
-嗨  -嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
-嘿  -你的服装也太让人称奇了
-Hey. -And your costume is blowing my mind.
-是吧  -算是吧
-Right? -Well, I guess.
问一下  你的装扮是
Um, who exactly are you supposed to be?
我妹妹  她就长这样
My sister. She looks like this.
哇  现在明白了
Wow. Now I get it.
我父母互相打扮成对方
My parents are dressed as each other.
-是啊  -这也让我想起了自己的父母
-Yeah. -You remind me a lot of my parents.
他们也喜欢这样瞎玩吗
Do they like to have fun too?
不是  这让我想起我有父  还有母
No, I meant that there are two of them.
好了  我们该走了
Well, we should get going.
-玩得开心  -是啊  再见
-Have fun. -Yeah. Bye.
哇  这姑娘是块瑰宝
Wow, she's a spark plug.
嘿  现在看碧昂斯·艾米特越来越顺眼了
Hey, Beyonce Emmett's looking better and better.
嘿  小鬼  那就是你的第二套服装吗
Hey, kiddo, that your second costume?
惨不忍睹啊
It's kinda lame.
好了  管他呢  第二次出动的目的就是扫荡糖果
Yeah, who cares? Second time around is all about volume.
-你想怎么样  -我想让你看点儿东西
-What do you want? -I want to show you something.
什么  这不是我干的
What? I didn't do this.
某人干的  我花了五十美元雇你保护这房子
Someone did, and I paid you $50 to <i>protect</i> my house.
但这不是我干的
But it wasn't me.
但是你要收拾干净
But it will be you cleaning it up.
哼  想都别想
Huh! I don't... I don't think so.
让我们仔细看看这份你签署的合同
Let's take a closer look at the contract you signed.
读这段
Right there.
“如果乙方  盖比·邓肯  保护住宅失败
"if provider, Gabe Duncan, fails to protect said residence,
乙方  盖比·邓肯  将同意给达布尼太太打工
The provider, Gabe Duncan, agrees to work for Mrs. Dabney.
一整天”  给你打什么工
For one full day..." work for you doing what?
-继续读  -“打工内容由达布尼太太拟定”
-Keep reading. -"...Doing whatever Mrs. Dabney tells him to."
-你耍我  -这就是我送给你的万圣节糖果
-You tricked me. -And that's my treat.
噢
Oh.
-别害怕  查莉  去要糖果  -去吧
-Go ahead, Charlie. Go get a piece of candy. -Go ahead.
-查莉  -我去追她
-Charlie! -I'll get her.
太有意思了
That was hilarious!
哪里有意思了  你变态吧
No, it wasn't. What is wrong with you?
你才变态呢  现在是万圣节
What's wrong with you? It's Halloween.
没错  但是吓一个两岁的小孩并不是有趣
Yeah, but scaring a two-year-old isn't funny.
-是卑鄙  -她才两岁
-It's mean. -She's only two?
抱歉  我并不知情
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
-拿着  多给你点儿糖果  -谢了
-Here, take some extra candy. -Thank you.
噢  搞什么
Oh! What?
卡尔  一分  捣蛋小鬼  零分
Karl, one; Trick-or-treaters, zero.
噢  这难闻的味道是什么
Oh, what is that horrible smell?
我在假血中加了点儿臭鸡蛋
I added some rotten eggs to the fake blood.
就好像我的独家酱料
It's kind of my secret sauce.
这身臭味让我怎么去派对啊
I can't go to a party smelling like this.
派对  再次抱歉  我并不知情
A party? I'm sorry. I didn't know.
去那口大锅里看看  里面有香水
Reach into the cauldron. There's some perfume in there.
噢  你爱弄就自己伸进你那口破锅里  你以为我傻啊
Oh, reach into your own cauldron, you clump nugget!
我讨厌那个叫卡尔的孩子
I hate that Karl kid!
你看看  在派对上没有一个人愿意和我说话
I mean, no one would even talk to me at the party.
你能怪他们吗  你变成了玛丽有点儿小味道
Can you blame them? Mary had a little smell.
我们要给好好教训那个卡尔一趟
We need to teach Karl a lesson.
好吧  但你能离远点儿说说么  你还臭着呢
Well, can you teach it from over there? You've still got a little stink on.
艾薇
Ivy,
我要复仇
I want revenge.
好吧  你的计划是什么
Okay, so what's your plan?
听听这个
How about this?
我弄一张印有卡尔的借书证
I get a library card in Karl's name,
然后我狂借图书
I check out a lot of books.
到还书日期后  我也不去还
And I keep them well past their due dates.
我承认  干这事我外行  帮帮我
Okay, I'm no good at this. Help me.
好吧  系好你的安全带
Okay, fasten your seat belt.
艾薇我要带你前去
Ivy's gonna introduce you to
黑暗世界
the dark side.
我讨厌十一月一号
I hate November 1st.
是啊  麦芽奶糖球要了你的小命
Yeah, that's the problem with malted milk balls...
一个太多  一千个又不够
One's too many and 1,000 aren't enough.
再也不吃糖了
No more candy ever again.
-吃了这块再说  -别动  不许吃
-Right after this piece. -Nuh-uh. That's it.
我把剩下的都扔了  看啊  牛奶糖
I'm throwing the rest out. Ooh, caramel.
嘿  大家早
Hey, everybody.
呃  你知道万圣节已经结束了  对吧
Uh, you do know Halloween's over.
那你为什么还这么打扮呢
Why are you still wearing your costume?
这不是我的打扮  这是我的新形象
This isn't my costume. This is my new look.
这么说来昨晚你没穿万圣节服装吗
So you weren't in costume last night?
我当然穿了  不记得了吗  假胡子
Well, sure I was. Hello, fake mustache?
-PJ  你现在是哥特人了吗  -没错
-P.J., you're a goth now? -That's right,
由于现在的我和以前的我  完全是相反的两个人
And because I'm the total opposite of what I used to be,
所以现在请叫我JP
From now on call me J.P.
如果真是相反
If you're the total opposite,
那我们能叫你阿尔伯特·爱因斯坦吗
shouldn't we call you Albert Einstein?
阿尔伯特什么
Albert who?
PJ  我真是不明白
<i>P.J., I don't understand.</i>
-你为什么要这样  -佐伊
-Why are you doing this? -Zoey.
噢  真相大白了
Oh. That's why.
嗨
Hi.
我觉着我更喜欢她的妹妹
I think I like the sister better.
完工了
Okay.
鸡蛋都擦干净了  我能歇会了吗
All the egg's gone. Can I take a break now?
别急  先让我查查合同
Hold on, let me check the contract.
不能
Nope.
好吧  还要干什么
All right, what's next?
你去给卡布德洗澡
I need you to give Kaboodle a bath.
我才不去给你的猫洗澡呢
I'm not giving your Cat a bath!
-还有什么活儿  -刷达布尼先生后背上的毛
-What else you got? -Shave Mr. Dabney's back.
到这儿来  小猫咪
Here, Kitty Kitty.
你的那只猫好像不喜欢洗澡
That Cat of yours does not like taking baths.
我知道  所以我才让你去
I know. That's why I had you do it.
好了  接下来干什么
All right, what... what's next?
你去给卡布德喂维他命
You need to give kaboodle his vitamin.
是让他咽下这些吗
Is he supposed to swallow this?
不是  让他从下边服用
Oh no, that goes in the other end.
如果你认为他光只是不喜欢洗澡
And if you thought he didn't like baths?
那你就大错特错了
Ooh!
嘿  我和佐伊现在要出去
Hey, Zoey and I are going out now.
别等我了  我们可能会回来得有点儿晚
Don't wait up. We'll be back kinda late.
-你们去哪啊  -本来我建议去玩迷你高尔夫
-Where are you kids off to? -Well, I suggested minigolf,
但是佐伊想去墓地
But Zoey wanted to go to the cemetery.
于是我们商量了下  决定去墓地
So we compromised... we're going to the cemetery.
-你是谁啊  -PJ啊
-Who are you? -I'm P.J.
不是
No.
多谢提醒我  我现在是JP了
Thank you for reminding me. I'm J.P. Now.
成了  别闹了  不管你是谁
Okay, well, whoever you are,
你确定要将哥特进行到底吗
Are you sure about this goth thing?
老爸  老妈  别担心
Mom, dad, don't worry.
我还是你们手心里的宝
I'm still the same guy you know and love.
噢  老妈  忘了说了  我用光了眼线膏
Oh, mom, by the way, I ran out of eyeliner.
然后用了点儿你的
And I had to borrow some of yours.
鲍伯  咱们怎么处理这件事
Bob, what are we gonna do about this?
-静观其变  -静观其变可不是我的风格
-Nothing. -Doing nothing isn't my thing.
相信我  PJ没事的
Trust me, P.J. Is gonna be just fine.
忘了拿指甲油了
Forgot my nail polish.
如果他真出事了  那我们还可以
And if he isn't, then we've got.
寄希望于其他孩子
All these other kids we can pin our hopes on.
好了  我完成了你所要求的任何事情
All right, I've done everything you've asked.
-我能走了吗  -说真的
-Can I go now? -Well,
这么美好的一天总是过得那么快
I hate to see a beautiful day end,
在你扔掉那些垃圾后  就可以离开了
But you can go after you take out that trash.
这都是些什么  鸡蛋纸盒
What's all this? Egg cartons,
卫生纸卷
Toilet paper rolls.
你陷害我
You set me up.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你往自己家里扔鸡蛋扔卫生纸
You egged and T.P.'d your own house.
是谁伤你这么深  让你对这个世界失去了信任
Who hurt you so bad that you can't trust?
算你狠  达布尼太太
Well played, Mrs. D.
你是一位可敬的对手
You are a worthy adversary.
你也是
As are you.
-明年此时  -不见不散
-Until next year? -I'll be here.
-你找我  -是的  卡尔  进来吧
-You wanted to see me? -Yeah, Karl, come on in.
进来吧  听着  你先坐下
Come on. Look, have a seat.
听好了  你要提防下我的朋友  泰迪
Listen, I've got to warn you about my friend Teddy.
你惹怒了一个不该被惹怒的人
You ticked off the wrong person.
那又如何  难道我现在要怕她不成
So what, I'm supposed to be afraid <i>her</i> now?
是非常的害怕
<i>Very</i>afraid.
她这人有问题
She has problems...
愤怒问题
Anger problems.
玛丽有只小羊羔有愤怒问题
Mary had a little lamb has anger problems?
没错  如果你惹怒了她的小羊羔
Yes, and when you messed with her little lamb,
玛丽就会吓得你魂飞魄散
Scary is where Mary is sure to go.
艾薇  我回来了
<i>Ivy, I'm back.</i>
噢  完蛋了  大事不好了
Oh no. Okay, this isn't good.
呆着别动  我来处理这件事
Stay here. I'll deal with this.
别生气  卡尔来了
<i>Don't get mad.</i> <i>Karl's here.</i>
什么  他还敢来
<i>What?! What, he's here?!</i>
是谁让他来的
<i>Who brought him</i> <i>into this house?!</i>
我只想让你们和解这件事
I just wanted to make peace.
我告诉过你不要掺和这件事
<i>I told you</i> <i>not to get involved!</i>
你要干什么
<i>What are you doing?</i>
放下  不要啊
<i>Put that down! No!</i>
哥们保重
Save yourself.
她疯了
She's not right.
你好啊  卡尔
Hello, Karl.
-别杀我  -噢  别害怕
-Don't hurt me. -Oh, don't worry.
马上  你就会没有知觉了
In a minute, you won't feel <i>anything.</i>
-怕了吧  -不要啊  对不起啊
-Ha! -Please, I'm sorry!
放我走吧
Let me go!
不要啊
No!
好样的  继续跑啊  卡尔
Yeah, you keep running, Karl!
永远都不要回来
And don't come back!
太棒了
That was awesome.
是你太棒了
You were awesome.
好计  妙计
Great plan, smart plan.
知道吗  你就是一个天才
You know, you're a genius.
噢  你才是天才
Oh, you're a genius.
-被锁外面了  -悲剧了
-Locked out? -Locked out.
“刚才我正睡意昏昏
"But the fact is I was napping,
（出自美国诗人，埃德加·爱伦·坡的诗歌《乌鸦》）
而你敲门又敲得那么轻
And so gently you came rapping,
你敲门又敲得那么轻
And so faintly you came tapping,
轻轻叩我房间的门环
Tapping at my chamber door,
我差点以为没听见你
<i>That I scarce was sure</i> <i>I heard you...</i>
说着我打开门扇
<i>Here I opened wide</i> <i>the door;</i>
-但惟有黑夜”  -马上回来
-<i>Darkness there..."</i> <i>-Be right back.</i>
“凝视着夜色幽幽
"Deep into that: darkness peering,
我站在门边惊惧良久
Long I stood there wondering, fearing,
-疑惑中似乎梦见从前没人...”  -老妈
-Doubting, dreaming dreams no mortal... " -Mom.
嗨  宝贝
Hi, sweetie.
你来这里做什么
What are you doing here?
噢  我是来
Oh, just...
缅怀某人
Paying my respects.
缅怀谁
To who?
伊齐基尔·费尺霍
Ezekiel Fitchhorn.
他一九二八年就死了
He died in 1928.
时间并不能抚平一切伤痛
Time does not heal all wounds.
说真的  老娘  你来干什么
Really, mom, what are you doing here?
噢  PJ  过来
Oh, P.J., come here.
-宝贝儿子  我担心你啊  -那就别担心了
-Honey, I'm worried about you. -Stop worrying.
这就是现在的我
This is who I am now.
这一切感觉和你格格不入
It just doesn't seem like <i>you.</i>
儿子  你现在身处墓地中央
Honey, you're in the middle of a cemetery.
晚上十一点的时候  你本应该在家睡觉
At 11:00 at night when you could be at home in bed.
-我的确喜欢早睡  -就是啊
-I do like to go to bed early. -I know,
因为你就不是个夜猫子
Because you're not a nighttime person.
是啊  我是个日猫子
I know. I'm a daytime person.
就是啊  看看你  一身黑
Aw. And look at you, all in black.
-我不喜欢黑色  我喜欢彩色  -就是啊
-Black isn't me. I like pastels. -Right.
儿子啊
Sweetie,
当你真的找对了人
When you're with the right person,
你是不用为了她而改变自己的
You don't have to change who you are.
那你为什么总想着改变老爸啊
Then why are you always trying to change dad?
因为那才是真实的我
Because that's who <i>I</i> am.
儿子  你绝对是个了不起的人
Honey, you are such a great guy,
就在某个地方  会有个非常幸运的女孩
And somewhere out there is a very lucky girl.
等待着你的出现  我向天发誓
Who will find that out. I promise.
-来抱抱  -谢谢了  老妈
-Come here. -Thanks, mom.
-你要和佐伊聊聊吗  -是啊
-So are you gonna talk to Zoey? -Yeah.
我要向她坦白
I've just gotta be honest with her,
就告诉她  我们彼此不适合对方
You know, tell her it's not working.
“为平息我心儿的悸跳...”
"So that now, to the still beating of my heart..."
条子来了  快跑
The police are here! Run!
你搞什么
What was that?
我不喜欢伤害别人
I don't like to hurt people.
这才是我
That's who I am.
听着  查莉  我的黑暗世界之旅收获颇丰
Well, Charlie, my trip to the dark side went very well.
-俺是引路人  -是啊
-I showed her the way. -Yeah.
结果发现我喜欢吓别人
Turns out I like scaring people,
而且还很在行
and I'm good at it.
那是相当的在行
<i>Really</i> good at it.
相当吓人的在行
<i>Scarily</i> good at it.
你歇歇吧  玛丽
Give it a rest, Mary.
好运喽  查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
幸会  幸会  幸会
Well, hello hello hello.
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
我是伊齐基尔·费尺霍的灵魂
I am the ghost of Ezekiel fitchhorn.
那晚你前来拜访
You paid me a visit the other night.
今天我前来回访
I'm here to return the favor.
-请进吧  -谢谢
-Come on in. -Why thank you.
说来  有人告诉过你
Say, has anyone ever told you.
你并非池中物吗
You're the bee's knees?
呃  我曾祖父
Uh, my great-grandfather.
那你愿意和一个鬼混叙叙旧吗
How would you like to make time with a ghost?
噢  齐克  我真是受宠若惊
Oh, Zeke, that's really flattering,
如果假设我再老九十岁  而且归西后
And if I was 90 years older and dead,
我绝对会同意的
I'd be all over that.
鉴于假设不成立
Since I'm not...
下次  只要说一句“谢谢你的好意”就可以了
<i>Next time, a simple note "Thank you" will suffice.</i>